<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on vamsi.blog</title>
    <link>http://vamsi.blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on vamsi.blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://vamsi.blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Manager Expectations</title>
      <link>http://vamsi.blog/posts/manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vamsi.blog/posts/manager/</guid>
      <description>You should have more expectations of your manager You are not doing any favors to your manager by making their life easy Doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you make their life hell but have clearly defined set of expectaions both way Usually the expectations only run one way, from manager to you &amp;ndash; it should be both ways What kind of expectations?  Time commitment Clear and direct feedback Informing you about promo decisions   Sometimes people hesitate to ask managers questions because it looks bad, this needs to change You should feel free to ask manager anything and the manager should give an honest answer without judging you (including &amp;ldquo;no, i cannot discuss that with you yet&amp;rdquo;) It is a mutual agreement Culture of not telling promo is a toxic one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Holidays</title>
      <link>http://vamsi.blog/posts/holidays2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vamsi.blog/posts/holidays2021/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>http://vamsi.blog/posts/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 10:22:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vamsi.blog/posts/markdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo shortcodes</title>
      <link>http://vamsi.blog/posts/shortcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 10:22:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vamsi.blog/posts/shortcodes/</guid>
      <description>Images  Dave Herring    Dave Herring   Github Gist  Youtube video   Tweet Hugo 0.24 Released: Big archetype update + @Netlify _redirects etc. file supporthttps://t.co/X94FmYDEZJ #gohugo #golang @spf13 @bepsays
&amp;mdash; GoHugo.io (@GoHugoIO) June 21, 2017  Vimeo   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Learned to Stop Procrastinating, &amp; Love Letting Go</title>
      <link>http://vamsi.blog/posts/procrastination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 10:21:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vamsi.blog/posts/procrastination/</guid>
      <description>The end of procrastination is the art of letting go.
I’ve been a lifelong procrastinator, at least until recent years. I would put things off until deadline, because I knew I could come through. I came through on tests after cramming last minute, I turned articles in at the deadline after waiting until the last hour, I got things done.
Until I didn’t. It turns out procrastinating caused me to miss deadlines, over and over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>http://vamsi.blog/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 12:14:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vamsi.blog/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>hello, world!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
